# Chui Wing Sze, Sherry

Flat E, 17/F, Block 5, Phase 2, Belvedere Garden, Tsuen Wan, HK

Tel: 9744-2082 Email: sherrycws@gmail.com

### **Personal Summary**

An undergraduate at the University of Hong Kong. Responsible, detail-oriented, willing to devote to work and able to work under pressure. Effectively work in a multi-task and team environment. Have good organizational skill and great interest in accounting. Specialize in accounting, administrative work and interacting with people. Fluent in Chinese, English and Mandarin. Proficiency in computer applications. Good commands of English and Chinese character inputs and Microsoft Office Suite.

#### Working experience

1/11/2012 - 31/3/2017 Senior Accounting Officer - Small business management (Promoted from Accounting Officer on 1 Jan 2016)

Full-time position in Lynks C.P.A. Limited

- Handling full sets of accounts for clients
- Preparing monthly consolidated management reports & performance variance report
- Handling daily payments, monthly payroll and MPF payments
- · Handling HR-related issue
- \* Liaisoning with colleagues in Mainland for handling China tax issue
- Preparing and completing Employer's Return of Remuneration & Pension submitting to IRD

4/7/2011 - 12/9/2012 Staff Accountant 2 (Promoted from Staff Accountant 1 on 1 Apr 2012)

Full-time position in Lak & Associates C.P.A. Limited

Handling audit iob

7/7/2010 - 14/4/2011

Administrative Officer

Full-time position in China.hk Intellectual Property Services Co., Ltd

- Processing of trademark and design applications worldwide under the supervision of senior members of the company
- General office administration
- Sales & marketing administration

27/7/2009 - 26/8/2009 Financial planning assistant

Summer Internship in Winnie Tsui & Company which works for Manulife International Limited

- Compiling and categorizing data, documenting and verifying reasonableness
- · Assisting in analysis of clients' personal financial situation, plans and objectives
- Participating in the development and analysis of financial strategies in clients' wealth management creation and protection.

# **Professional Memberships**

Student member, Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) (papers F1 - F9, P2 - P3 passed)

# **Public Certification**

2017 Advanced Diploma in Accounting and Business, ACCA 2009 Insurance Intermediaries Qualifying Examination, papers I & III

Level 3 Certificate in Accounting, LCCI 2007

Pass with Distinction

### Education

2007-2010 One major in Risk Management and one major in Finance, Bachelor of Science, The University of Hong Kong

2005-2007 Liu Po Shan Memorial College

2000-2005 Ho Fung College

# Result of Hong Kong Advanced Level Examination (HKALE)

Principles of Accounts В **Pure Mathematics** R Use of English D Chinese Language and Culture D

### References

Ms. Shirley Ng, the Director Ms. Carrie Hui, the Director Lynks C.P.A. Limited Lak & Associates C.P.A. Limited

Contact no: 2526-5511 Contact no: 2815-8218

Available date: Sep 27, 2017 Present salary: \$25,000 Expected salary: negotiable